Guide to the Professor William C. Moffit Papers
University of Houston Libraries
- Marching Band Shows and Materials
  - Marching Band Shows
    This sub-series contains 2 boxes of material including the marching schematics of various shows that William C. Moffit was responsible for putting together for a variety of occasions. This material includes various pregame shows for the 1979 Cotton Bowl and other football games. The series is arranged chronologically and alphabetically, as indicated. Original folder and item order has been maintained whenever possible. Exceptions were made when folders were obviously misfiled or when no order was apparent.
    - Wildcat Dancing Band, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Show No. 5; MSU vs. Notre Dame at Southbend; National T.V. N.B.C., 1964 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Show No. 2: Michigan State vs. U of M, October 10, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Tampa Show, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - 128 Piece Band Show for Cunics, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - 192 Piece Show, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Special Show for 32-48-64, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Cotton Bowl Show, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Pregame First Show No. 4; “Patterns of Motion” Show, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - “Circus Show”; 96 Piece Band, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - “Patterns of Motion” Show; 96 Piece Band, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - “Showboat Show”, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - “Twin Bands Show”, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Patriotic Show, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - “Armed Forces Show”; 96 Piece Band, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - “Beatles Show”, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - “Sweet Charity Show”, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - 160 Piece Band Show Book (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - “Americana Show” (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - “Big Band Show” (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - “Block Band Drill Techniques” (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - “Bugler’s Dream”; Formations (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - “Circus Entry” (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - “Conquest Entry” (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - “First Show No. 1” (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - “First Show No. 2” (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - “First Show No. 3; A “Patterns of Motion” Show (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - “First Show No. 86” (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - “From This Moment On” (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Illinois Game Formations (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Iowa Fight Song (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - I.S.U 96 Piece Show (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - “It’s All Right with Me”; Squad Line Up (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Master Charts (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - “Music Spectacular Show” (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - “New Patterns of Motion Show” (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - “New Patterns Show” (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - “Old Man River” (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - Patterns of Motion; 96 Piece Band (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - Pre-Game Show (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - Purdue “Spell-Out” (Box 33, Folder 41)
    - “Rock-a-Bye Your Baby”; Formations (Box 33, Folder 42)
    - Salute to “American Show-Biz” (Box 33, Folder 43)
    - “Show No. 1”; 80 Piece Band Show (Box 33, Folder 44)
    - “Show No. 1”; 160 Piece Band “Patterns of Motion”, undated (Box 33, Folder 45)
    - “Show No. 2; Otterbein, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 46)
    - “Show No. 3”; Otterbein; “Farewell 85”, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 47)
    - “Show No. 2”, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 48)
    - Show No. 3; Purdue vs. Illinois (Box 33, Folder 49)
    - Show No. 4; “Statue of Liberty Show” (Box 33, Folder 50)
    - Show No. 4; Purdue vs. Illinois, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 51)
    - Show No. 4; “Pop Songs”, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 52)
    - Show No. 5; “Finale”, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 53)
    - Show No. 5; PU vs. OSU; “Celebration of a Century”, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 54)
    - Show No. 6, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 55)
    - Show No. 6, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 56)
    - Show No. 7, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 57)
    - Show No. 9, undated (Box 33, Folder 58)
    - Show No. 10, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 59)
    - Show No. 11, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 60)
    - Show No. 12; “Tonight”, undated (Box 33, Folder 61)
    - Show No. 13, undated (Box 33, Folder 62)
    - Show No. 14; “A Patterns of Motion Show”, undated (Box 33, Folder 63)
    - Show No. 15, undated (Box 33, Folder 64)
    - Show No. 16; “A Patterns of Motion Show”, undated (Box 33, Folder 65)
    - Show No. 17, undated (Box 33, Folder 66)
    - Show No. 17; “A Patterns of Motion Show”, undated (Box 33, Folder 67)
    - Show No. 18, undated (Box 33, Folder 68)
    - Show No. 19, undated (Box 33, Folder 69)
    - Show No. 20; “Patriotic Show” (Box 33, Folder 70)
    - Show No. 21; “A John Lennon Salute”, undated (Box 33, Folder 71)
    - Show No. 21; “A John Lennon Salute”, undated (Box 33, Folder 72)
    - Show No. 22; “Hello Dolly”, undated (Box 33, Folder 73)
    - Show No. 22; “Maxi-Mini Show”, undated (Box 33, Folder 74)
    - Show No. 23; “Hey Look Me Over”, undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Show No. 23; “Pops Show”, undated (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Show No. 24, undated (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Show No. 24; 96 Piece Band, undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Show No. 25; “Alumni Show”, undated (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Show No. 26, undated (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Show No. 27; “Patriotic Show”, undated (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Show No. 31; “Fire Your Best Show", undated (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Show No. 31; “Fire Your Best Show”, undated (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Show No. 35; “The Band of Tomorrow”, undated (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - “Sound of Tomorrow – Today” Show, undated (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Patterns of Motion Material
    Patterns of Motion, by William C. Moffit, was a marching style featuring band members in constantly changing kaleidoscope patterns. This new marching band style, created by Moffit, quickly became a new trend and continues to impact contemporary marching band styles. This sub-series contains some basic formation designs that make up “Patterns of Motion.” It is arranged alphabetically and consists of 2 boxes. Oversized Patterns of Motion material may be found in OVS Box 59. Original folder and item order has been maintained whenever possible. Exceptions were made when folders were obviously misfiled or when no order was apparent.
    - 64 Piece ID’s (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - 96 Piece Band; “Computer Shows with Music (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - 96 Piece ID’s (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - 112 Piece ID’s (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Advanced Technique Combinations (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - “Auld Lang Syne” (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Basic Patterns Concepts (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Basic Pattern Charting (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Block (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Block Band (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Block Band Triangles (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - “Buffalo Bills” (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Cecilia Choreography (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Can Can; Fancy Footwork Instructions (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Circus Show (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Circus Show; 96 Piece Band (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Cleveland Show; Cleveland Stadium, October 12, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Company Front Action (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Concert Formations (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Concert Formations (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Diagonal Designs (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Diagonal Squad Stagings (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - Do Lord (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - Double Designs (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - Drum Scoring Examples (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - E Flat Trumpet Concepts; page 1 and page 2 (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - Expanding/Contracting Action (Box 34, Folder 38)
    - Fall in Fanfare (Box 34, Folder 39)
    - Fancy Footwork (Box 34, Folder 40)
    - Fanfare Position; Start That Old Black Magic (Box 34, Folder 41)
    - Field Entry Procedures (Box 34, Folder 42)
    - First Show (Box 34, Folder 43)
    - Halftime (Box 34, Folder 44)
    - Head Medley (Box 34, Folder 45)
    - I Only Want to Be With You (Box 34, Folder 46)
    - Jim Sanders (Box 34, Folder 47)
    - John Muskrat (Box 34, Folder 48)
    - Mame; Bass Line Study (Box 34, Folder 49)
    - March America (Box 34, Folder 50)
    - Marching Band Personnel, 1976-1977 (Box 34, Folder 51)
    - Marching Miscellaneous (Box 34, Folder 52)
    - Marching Miscellaneous II (Box 34, Folder 53)
    - Melody Variations; Changes; Swing Low (Box 34, Folder 54)
    - Michigan State University; Marching Band Handbook (Box 34, Folder 55)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 34, Folder 56)
    - Mosaics (Box 34, Folder 57)
    - Mosaics; Designs (Box 34, Folder 58)
    - 59 MSU vs. Indiana; Veteran’s Day, November 11, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 59)
    - New Patterns Ideas (Box 34, Folder 60)
    - Old Man River (Box 34, Folder 61)
    - Patriotic Show (Box 34, Folder 62)
    - Patterns for Percussion (Box 34, Folder 63)
    - Patterns for Percussion; Volume I (Box 34, Folder 64)
    - Patterns for Percussion; Volume II; No. 1 (Box 34, Folder 65)
    - Patterns for Percussion; Volume II; No. 2 (Box 34, Folder 66)
    - Patterns of Motion (Box 34, Folder 67)
    - Patterns of Motion (Box 34, Folder 68)
    - Patterns of Motion; 64 Piece Band; Book 3 - now catalogued (Box 34, Folder 69)
    - Patterns of Motion; 128 Piece Band Book; Planning Master (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Patterns of Motion; Basic Fundamentals by Bill Moffit (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Patterns of Motion; Field Sequence Planning Charts (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Patterns of Motion; Full Field “Squad Size”; Quadruple Field Planning Charts (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Patterns of Motion; Master Planning Guide; Book 2 - now catalogued (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Patterns of Motion; Master Planning Guide; Book 2; Kaleidoscopes II (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Patterns of Motion; Master Planning Guide; Book 2; Kaleidoscopes I (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Patterns of Motion; Master Planning Guide; Book 3 - now catalogued (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Patterns of Motion; Show (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Patterns of Motion; Techniques Workshop (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Patterns Rudimental Drill; Instant Letters (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Pigskin Pageant of 1957 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Pigskin Pageant of K.H.S.; Script; 1959 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Pregame Onward Christian (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Rock-A-Bye Your Baby (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Show No. 2 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Showboat Show (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Rock-A-Bye Your Baby (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Show No. 19; “A Bill Moffit Patterns Show” (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Show Planning Tools (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Sliding Squad Actions (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Silverado (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Something for Cat (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Soundpower Book Program (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Soundpower Page 1 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Soundpower Page 2 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Soundpower Page 3 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Soundpower Page 4 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Soundpower Page 5 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Soundpower Page 6 (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Soundpower Page 7 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Soundpower Page 8 (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - Soundpower; “Patterns for Percussion” (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - Soundpower Scoring Techniques (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - Spinning Letters (Box 35, Folder 35)
    - Split Field Master (Box 35, Folder 36)
    - Spiritual Show; Patterns Showcase Series (Box 35, Folder 37)
    - Start of “Oh Babe” (Box 35, Folder 38)
    - St. Elmo’s Fire (Box 35, Folder 39)
    - Start of “Sing-Sing-Sing” (Box 35, Folder 40)
    - Step 2 – Step 4; Action Company Fronts (Box 35, Folder 41)
    - The Band of Tomorrow Show (Box 35, Folder 42)
    - The Cleveland Browns “Show”, November 25, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 43)
    - The Hardin County Fair Marching Band Show, September 26, 1957 (Box 35, Folder 44)
    - The Rhythm of Life (Box 35, Folder 45)
    - Twin Band Show (Box 35, Folder 46)
    - Vertical Company Front Untitled (Box 35, Folder 47)
    - Action (Box 35, Folder 48)
    - “Wildcat” Marching Band, 1954 (Box 35, Folder 49)
    - America, Evergreen, You'll Never Walk Alone, GL Fight or Drums (Ovs box 59, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Slides (music on paper, sheet metal, and transparencies) (Ovs box 59, Folder 2)
  - School Shows
    This sub-series contains 2 boxes of shows performed by school bands under the direction of William C. Moffit. Material is arranged chronologically coinciding with Moffit’s career.
    - Kenton High School, 1958 Season (Box 35, Folder 50)
    - MSU vs. Northwestern University; Pregame and Half-Time Show; Final Show, 1967 Season (Box 35, Folder 51)
    - MSU vs. Illinois; Halftime Show No. 1, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 52)
    - MSU vs. Michigan; Halftime Show No. 2, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 53)
    - MSU vs. Ohio State; Halftime Show No. 3, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - MSU vs. Northwestern; Halftime Show No. 4; Homecoming Game, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - MSU vs. Indiana; Halftime Show No. 5, November 13, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - MSU vs. Notre Dame; Halftime Show No. 6, November 20, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - “I Could Have Danced All Night” (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - MSU Band, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - MSU Band; Slaughter Show, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - MSU Marching Band; Master Planning Book, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - MSU vs. University of Michigan; Pregame and Halftime Shows, October 8, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - MSU to Block (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - MSU vs. Indiana; Halftime Show No. 7, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - MSU vs. Notre Dame; 1966; Final Game ’66 Season; East Lansing; November 19; Regional IV (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - MSU vs. Purdue; Halftime Show No. 8, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - MSU vs. Southern California; Halftime Show No. 1, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - MSU vs. Wisconsin; Halftime Show No. 2; 1967; Hits of the Season; Purdue vs. Indiana, 1967;1982 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - “Night and Day” (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - “Night Train” (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - “Nittany” (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - “Not from Dixie” (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - “Notre Dame at MSU (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Patriotic Show “83”; Show No. 4; MSU; 1964; Purdue, November 7, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Patterns of Motion Spiritual Show; 321 Piece Band; Master Chart Book (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - “Patterns of Motion”; Squad Marching Assignments; 96 Step Kaleidoscope (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Pregame Block Entry (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Pregame Entrance, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Pregame Points (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Pregame Show Charts; MSU vs. Illinois, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Pregame Tunnel Entrance Lineup”; MSU, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Rosebowl Show; Spartan Marching Band, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - “Saints” (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - “Silvery Moon” (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Show No. 3; MSU vs. Michigan, October 14, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - Show No. 4; 1966; Purdue vs. Iowa; MSU vs. Purdue; 1982, November; East Lansing Regional IV, October 27, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 33)
    - Show No. 6; MSU vs. Illinois, November 14, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - “Slaughter on Tenth Avenue” (Box 36, Folder 35)
    - “Something for Cat” (Box 36, Folder 36)
    - “Spartan Drums” (Box 36, Folder 37)
    - Spartan Marching Band; Weekly Show Charts, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 38)
    - Spinning “S” (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - “Swanee” (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - “That Old Black Magic” (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - “This Land is Your Land” (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - “Toot-Toot Tootsie” (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - 1st Patterns Show in Houston, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Blue Bonnet Bowl Show, 1971-1972 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Cotton Bowl Show, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Cotton Bowl Show, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - UH vs. Arkansas; Halftime Show. No. 4; Rice Stadium, October 23, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - University of Arkansas; Homecoming; Halftime Show No. 4; Home, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - UH vs. A&M; Halftime Show No. 2; Rice Stadium, September 25, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - UH vs. A&M; Halftime Show No. 3; Houston, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - UH vs. A&M and SMU; Halftime Show No. 3; “Broadway’s Best”, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - UH vs. Auburn; Halftime Show No. 4, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - UH vs. Baylor; Halftime Show No. 1, September 11, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - UH vs. Baylor; Halftime Show No. 2, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - UH vs. Baylor; Halftime Show NO. 3, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - UH vs. Baylor and NTSU; Halftime Show No. 2; “Latin America Show”, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - UH vs. Blinn Junior College; Halftime Show No. 3, October 5, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - UH vs. Cincinnati; Halftime Show No. 4, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - UH vs. Colorado State; Homecoming, November 11, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - UH vs. Florida State; Halftime Show No. 4; Homecoming, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - UH vs. Florida State; Halftime Show No. 4; Homecoming, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - UH vs. Florida State; Halftime Show No. 6; Interfaith and High School Senior Day, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - UH vs. Florida; Halftime Show No. 1; Bandnight Pregame, September 15, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - UH vs. ISU; Halftime Show No. 2, July 15, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - UH vs. University of Memphis State; Homecoming Show, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - UH vs. University of Miami; Halftime Show No. 2; Regional TV; Astrodome, November 1, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - UH vs. University of Miami; Halftime Show No. 2; ABCTV; Home, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - UH vs. UM; Halftime Show No. 2, October 25, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - UH vs. University of Nebraska; Cotton Bowl Show, January 1, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - UH vs. New Mexico; Halftime Show No. 5, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 33)
    - UH vs. North Carolina State; Blue Bonnet Bowl Show, December 23, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 34)
    - UH vs. Rice University; First Game, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 35)
    - UH vs. Rice University; Halftime Show No. 1, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 36)
    - UH vs. Rice University; Halftime Show No. 7, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 37)
    - UH vs. Rice University; Halftime Show No. 7; “Hits of the Season”, December 1, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 38)
    - UH vs. SMU; Halftime Show No. 3; Homecoming Show, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 39)
    - UH vs. TCU; Halftime Show No. 6; Drill Team Invitational, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 40)
    - UH vs. TCU; Pregame and Halftime Show; Homecoming, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 41)
    - UH. vs. Texas; Halftime Show No. 5; Rice Stadium, January 15, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 42)
    - UH vs. Texas; Halftime Show No. 5, November 10, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 43)
    - UH vs. Texas; Oilers vs. New England; Halftime Show No. 6, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 44)
    - UH vs. Texas Tech; Halftime Show No. 7, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 45)
    - UH vs. Texas Tech; Halftime Show No. 6, November 19, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 46)
    - UH vs. UCLA “Dome”; Halftime Show No. 1, September 12, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 47)
    - UH vs. Utah; Halftime Show No. 1; Bandnight Pregame, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 48)
    - UH vs. Villanova; Halftime Show No. 3, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - UH vs. Virginia Tech; Halftime Show No. 3, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - UH vs. West Texas; Halftime Show No. 2, September 29, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - UH vs. University of Wyoming; Halftime Show No. 4, November 22, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - “1st Half of Fight Song” (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - “Alabama All-State Band” (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - “Alexander’s Ragtime Band” (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - All American Marching Band; Purdue, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - All American Marching Band Show, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - “Always True to You” (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - “Another Opening, Another Show” (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - “Billboard Chaser” (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Block Band Assignments; Pregame Show, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Block Band to Pre-SC-Formation (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - “Can Can” (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - “Clinic Show”; Patterns of Motion; 64 Piece Band; Haslett High School Band; Win-Blackford-Dir, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - “Coming Up Roses” (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Cougar Marching Band; Pregame Show Book, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Cougar Marching Band; Squad Personnel, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Downfield Maneuver (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - End of Cadence Fanfare (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Florida All-State Band (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Florida All-State Band Show, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - “Fight On” (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - “Fight Song”; start (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - “From the “S” to the Block (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - “From This Moment On” (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - “Get Ready” (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - “Hits of the Season”; Show No. 5, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - “Hits of the Season”, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - “I Love Paris” (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - “It’s All Right With Me” (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - “It’s So Easy” (Box 38, Folder 33)
    - “Joshua” (Box 38, Folder 34)
    - “King of the Road” (Box 38, Folder 35)
    - “Light My Fire” (Box 38, Folder 36)
    - “Lover” (Box 38, Folder 37)
    - Marching Band Music Performance Listing, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 38)
    - Marching Band Performance Listings, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 39)
    - Marching Band Performance Listings, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 40)
    - Music List; Halftime Music Performance, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 41)
    - New Patterns of Motion “Basics” (Box 38, Folder 42)
    - “Purdue Intros” (Box 38, Folder 43)
    - “Purdue University All-American Marching Band Music Performance DA-TA, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 44)
    - “Purdue University All-American Marching Band”; Halftime; Pregame, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 45)
  - Miscellaneous
    This sub-series contains 106 folders of basic formations and fully mapped shows created by William C. Moffit. Material includes specific university shows as well as limited edition director’s guides. Material is arranged alphabetically. Original folder and item order has been maintained whenever possible. Exceptions were made when folders were obviously misfiled or when no order was apparent.
    - 80 Piece Band Show No. 2 (Box 38, Folder 46)
    - 96 Piece Band Show; Otterbein ’85 – Show No. 1; “Step 2” Show; “Alley Cat” – A.B.C. Football; “Wabash Blues”; “Much Grandioso” (Box 38, Folder 47)
    - 96 Piece Band Show; Otterbein, Show 2, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 48)
    - 96 Step Kaleidoscope (Box 38, Folder 49)
    - 128 Piece Band IDS (Box 38, Folder 50)
    - 144 Piece Band IDS (Box 38, Folder 51)
    - 192 Piece Band IDS (Box 38, Folder 52)
    - “Basic Staging Designs” (Box 38, Folder 53)
    - Charting Worksheet; No. 1 Peanut Pattern (Box 38, Folder 54)
    - Circular Formations (Box 38, Folder 55)
    - #7, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 56)
    - Show #2, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 57)
    - Show #3 Band Day Pregame, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 58)
    - Show #1, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 59)
    - Show #3 Band Night Pregame, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 60)
    - Band Day Show; Pregame Charts, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 61)
    - “Circus Entry” (Box 38, Folder 62)
    - “Cogswheel Base Staging” (Box 38, Folder 63)
    - College Band Directors Association; Austin, Texas, January 30, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 64)
    - Company Front Slant and Pick-Up Evolving Effects (Box 38, Folder 65)
    - Concert Formations (Box 38, Folder 66)
    - Concert Formation; Multi Pattern Charting (Box 38, Folder 67)
    - Continuous Visual Action (Box 38, Folder 68)
    - “Conversions” (Box 38, Folder 69)
    - Cotton Bowl; UH vs. Nebraska, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 70)
    - Cougar Pregame Entrance; Spinning UH, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 71)
    - 12“Concert Formations” (Box 38, Folder 72)
    - Cross Base Staging (Box 38, Folder 73)
    - Diagonal Staging; 64 Piece Band (Box 38, Folder 74)
    - 15“Diagonals” (Box 38, Folder 75)
    - “Double Action Layering” (Box 38, Folder 76)
    - Fall In Position (Box 38, Folder 77)
    - First Show No. 4; “That’s Entertainment”; “Alley Cat”; “Superstar”; Leonard, Hal, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 78)
    - 18 Field Day Entry Procedures (Box 38, Folder 79)
    - 19 Field Entrance Techniques; Patterns in Sequence Fall in Position (Box 38, Folder 80)
    - 20 File Pattern Basics” (Box 38, Folder 81)